// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is Truncation in Java?",
    answer: "Floating-point value assigned to an integer type",
    options: [
      "Floating-point value assigned to a Floating type",
      "Floating-point value assigned to an integer type",
      "Integer value assigned to floating type",
      "Integer value assigned to floating type"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the extension of compiled java classes?",
    answer: ".class",
    options: [
      ".txt",
      ".js",
      ".class",
      ".java"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which exception is thrown when java is out of memory?",
    answer: "OutOfMemoryError",
    options: [
      "MemoryError",
      "OutOfMemoryError",
      "MemoryOutOfBoundsException",
      "MemoryFullException"
      ]
      
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of these are selection statements in Java?",
    answer: "if()",
    options: [
      "break",
      "continue",
      "for()",
      "if()"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of these keywords is used to define interfaces in Java?",
    answer: "interface",
    options: [
      "intf",
      "Intf",
      "interface",
      "Compilation"
    ]
  },
   {
     numb: 6,
     question: "Which of the following is a superclass of every class in Java?",
     answer: "Object class",
     options: [
       "ArrayList",
       "Abstract class",
       "Object class",
       "String"
     ]
   },
    {
     numb: 7,
     question: "Which of the below is not a Java Profiler?",
     answer: "JVM",
     options: [
       "JProfiler",
       "Eclipse Profiler",
       "JVM",
       " JConsole"
     ]
   },
   {
     numb: 8,
     question: "Which of these packages contains the exception Stack Overflow in Java?",
     answer: "java.lang",
     options: [
       "java.io",
       "java.system",
       "java.lang",
       "java.util"
     ]
   },
  {
     numb: 9,
     question: "Which of these statements is incorrect about Thread?",
     answer: "run() method is used to begin execution of a thread before start() method in special cases",
     options: [
       "start() method is used to begin execution of the thread",
       "run() method is used to begin execution of a thread before start() method in special cases",
       "A thread can be formed by implementing Runnable interface only",
       "A thread can be formed by a class that extends Thread class"
     ]
   },
   {
     numb: 10,
     question: "Which of these keywords are used for the block to be examined for exceptions?",
     answer: "try",
     options: [
       "check",
       "throw",
       "catch",
       "try"
     ]
   },
];